http://www.pixelink.com/support/compliance/privacy-statement/

Company
About
Why Choose Pixelink?
Camera Software
Software Development Kit (SDK)
Compliance & Certifications
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
Privacy Statement
Pixelink, A Navitar® Company, respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. This privacy statement explains our policies and practices while you visit our site. Through this disclosure, we intend to provide you a level of comfort and confidence in how we collect, use and safeguard personal and other information that we collect or that you provide through this website. By using the site, you agree to the terms of this privacy statement.
Data Collected
We collect two types of information: personal and demographic. Personal information is any information that is specific to your identification such as name, address, phone number, email, payment card and resumes. Demographic information is information that cannot be associated with you personally such as, domain information, zip codes, and areas of interest.
Use of Data
When you request a service, place an order, submit feedback, submit a resume, or download a file, it is necessary for you to offer certain personal information about yourself so that we may serve your needs. We will not send you information unless you specifically request it or we feel that the information would benefit your business needs. If you decide that you do not want to receive further information, simply contact us and request to be removed from the contact list. When you order a sample from us, a customer representative may contact you. The demographic information collected through our site is used to evaluate how our site is used and how it can be improved. It may also be used for marketing, recruiting, and investment analysis.
Access to your Personal Information
Our web site allows you to set up a personal account to interact with the company, e.g. to place orders or apply for a job. You may access your personal account to change your personal information.
Cookies
Some features of this site use cookies. Cookies are small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. If your browser is set to accept cookies, then your browser adds the text in a small file. Please note that cookies cannot read information on your hard drive. We use cookies to measure our web trafficking processes, so that we may make our site more efficient. We also use cookies to offer you certain services and to customize your visit, and we may use third-party service providers who may use cookies to support our effort to improve our site. You may choose to turn off cookies completely, but you will not be able to use certain site services, such as the shopping cart.
If you are a registered user, you can specifically request that our site remembers your login information. By doing so, you are allowing us to place a permanent cookie onto your computer.
We use software such as Google Analytics, a first-party cookie that allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, source and time spent on website. The information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. This will help to protect your privacy. Using software such as Google Analytics, we can see what content is popular on our website, and strive to give you more of the things you enjoy reading and watching. To opt out of Google Analytics analytic cookies across Navitar websites visit: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before a cookie is placed. If you choose not to accept cookies, you may have to manually input user IDs and passwords to receive certain data.
Creating Log-in Credentials
Certain pages of this website may allow you to create login credentials by creating a user name/ID and password. When you become a registered user you are allowing us to place a permanent cookie onto your computer.
You may choose to turn off cookies completely, but you will not be able to use certain site services, such as the shopping cart.
Social Media
Our site includes areas where you can provide comments about our products and services, and includes links to social media sites that also allow you to post comments about our products and services. Any comments that you post are visible to the public and thus you should have no expectation of privacy with regard to information that you post. We monitor our social media sites and may delete any comments that are offensive, contain links to irrelevant blogs or websites, or are completely unrelated. Also, the third party social media sites that provide platforms for our information have their own privacy policies that govern their sites.
Security
Systems that store your information are firewall protected. Access to sensitive information is restricted to authorized personnel. If we ask for any credit card or financial information, this information is transmitted through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which encrypts sensitive information. Information that is transmitted between our site and our registered users is also SSL encrypted.
Contact Us Today
Company
About
Why Choose Pixelink?
Leadership Team
Careers
Events
News
A Navitar Company
Applications
OEM Markets
Machine Vision
Compliance & Certifications
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
Information Resources
Returns and RMAs
Hardware and Software Partners
Contact Support
Contact
Find a Dealer
Become a Pixelink Dealer
Request a Quote
Contact Sales
Newsletter Signup
Portal Login Info
1-833-247-1211
©Copyright 2020 Pixelink. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy.
Company
About
Why Choose Pixelink?
Leadership Team
Careers
Events
News
A Navitar Company
Applications
OEM Markets
Machine Vision
Compliance & Certifications
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
Information Resources
Returns and RMAs
Hardware and Software Partners
Contact Support
Contact
Find a Dealer
Become a Pixelink Dealer
Request a Quote
Contact Sales
Newsletter Signup
Portal Login Info
This website uses cookies to store information on your computer. Some of these cookies are used for visitor analysis, others are essential to making our site function properly and improve the user experience. By using this site, you consent to the placement of these cookies. Click Accept to consent and dismiss this message. Read our Privacy Statement for more information.
Accept
